A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers and OK Harris Works of Art gallery records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art AAA.okharr
Archives of American Art
- Artwork, 1970s-circa 1980s; Series 6; 0.8 Linear feet Box 44, OV 81-OV 87
  This series consists of 40 prints by OK Harris artists. With the exception of two black and white prints, all are color lithographs. Radical Realism I is a set of six signed and numbered prints (an edition of 200) by John Clem Clarke, Richard Estes, Ralph Goings, Richard McLean, Malcolm Morley, and John Salt issued by Mother Lode Editions in 1972. Other color lithographs are by John Baeder, Robert Bechtle, Davis Cone, Ralph Goings, Randy Green, H. N. Han, John Kacere, Richard McLean, Naoto Nakagawa, and John Salt; one bears an illegible signature.
  Correspondence (Series 1) includes small drawings and other artwork enclosed with a number of number of artists' letters to Ivan and Marilynn Karp, a variety of hand made holiday cards, and some illustrated letters. A small amount of artwork also is scattered among the artists' files (Series 4).
  - Black and White Prints by Douglas Bond and Roger A. Bultot, undated; Oversized prints housed in OV 81 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Color Lithographs, Radical Realism I, 1972; Oversized color lithographs housed in OV 81 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Color Lithographs, 1970s-circa 1980; undated; Oversized color lithographs housed in OV 82 - OV 85 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Oversized Black and White Prints by Douglas Bond and Roger A. Bultot from Box 44, Folder 12, undated (Box OV 81)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Radical Realism I, from Box 44, Folder 13, 1972 (Box OV 81)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Bader - Bechtle, from Box 44, Folder 14, undated; 1974 (Box OV 82)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Cone, from Box 44, Folder 14, undated (Box OV 83)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Goings, from Box 44, Folder 14, 1970s-circa 1980 (Box OV 84)
  - Oversized Lithographs, Green - Nakagawa, from Box 44, Folder 14, undated (Box OV 85)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Kacere, from Box 44, Folder 14, 1977; undated (Box OV 86)
  - Oversized Color Lithographs, Salt - Unidentified, from Box 44, Folder 14, undated (Box OV 87)
- Photographic Materials, bulk 1969-1999; 1960s-2014; Series 7; 32 Linear feet Boxes 44-76
  Photographic materials consist of photographs, slides, negatives, and digital images of artwork by artists associated with OK Harris Works of Art and views of the gallery's exhibition installations from 1960s-2014. The majority of photographs and slides carry identifying information, e.g., titles, dates, media, and photographic credits.
  Artists' photo books consist of copy prints of artwork by 59 artists actively represented by OK Harris Works of Art and by artists formerly associated with the gallery. Artists' slides are of artwork that was exhibited at OK Harris and other galleries from the 1960s-2000s.
  Installation views preserved in 61 binders document solo exhibitions and other shows presented at OK Harris during its 45 year history. Negatives of OK Harris installations photographed by Eric Pollitzer and Dan Lenore include numbered references, but no key is included. Other installation views include exhibitions by gallery artists at other venues, e.g., the Brevard Museum, New England College and the Studio Art Centers International.
  Photographs of miscellaneous subjects include a photo book of the gallery's artists exhibiting at art expositions, art fairs, and museums, among them Tokyo Art Expo (1991), the Nevada Institute for Contemporary Art (1994), and the Chicago Art Fair (1999, 2002). Of particular interest are photographs of exhibition openings at 19 Galerie Des 4 Mouvements in Paris and at Galerie de Gestlo in Dusseldorf held during the 1970s. Also found are loose miscellaneous photographs, and an album of photographs of the OK Harris Works of Art galleries, office, and staff including Ivan Karp.
  The original order of the material has been maintained. Artists' slides are labeled as "Group A" and "Group B." According to gallery staff, the groupings relate to the time artists needed to produce enough new work for an exhibition. Many, but not all volumes are numbered, and damaged binders have been dismantled. Additional photographic materials are included among the artists' files (Series 4) and with Ivan C. Karp's personal papers (Series 8 ). This series is arranged as 4 subseries:
  7.1: Artists' Photo Books - Current and Past, 1969-2014, bulk 1969-1995
  7.2: Artists' Slides - Current and Past, 1969-2000s
  7.3: Installation Views, 1969-circa 2011
  7.4: Photographs - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1970s-2000s
  - Artists' Photo Books, bulk 1969-1999; circa 1969-circa 2014; 7.1
    - Artists' Photo Books - Current (Box 44)
      - Baeder, John, Volumes I-IV, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 44, Folder 15-18)
      - Castanis, Muriel, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Chard, Daniel, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Cho, Y. J., circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Constantine, Greg, [Volume 1]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 4-5)
      - Del Grosso, James, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Dudley, Randy, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
      - Dufresne, Leonard, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - Fox, Stephen, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn, [Volume 1]-Volume IV, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 46, Folder 4-7)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn, Volumes V-XI, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 47, Folder 1-7)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn - Necklace (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - German, Vladimir, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Giese, David, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Ginder, Robert, circa 1969- circa 2014 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Goings, Ralph, [Volume 1]-IV, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 48, Folder 5-8)
      - Goings, Ralph, Volume V, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Gozu, Masao, circa 1969- circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Kacere, John, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
      - Lynds, Clyde, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Matthews, Ben, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - McLean, Richard, Volume I, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - McLean, Richard, Volumes II-III, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
      - Mendenhall, Richard, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Morgan, Kenneth, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Nichols, William, [Volume I]-Volume 2, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
      - Richbourg, Lance, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Rohm, Robert, Volumes I-VI, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 51, Folder 1-6)
      - Saari, Peter, Volume I, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Saari, Peter, Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Salt, John, Volumes I-III, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 52, Folder 2-4)
      - Sato, Masaaki, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Szeto, Keung, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Van Vranken, Robert, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Weis, Ron - Dismantled Binder, circa 1969-circa 2014; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 53, Folder 1-3)
      - Zago, Tino, Volumes I-II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
    - Artists' Photo Books - Past (Box 53)
      - Adams, Allan, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Baladi, Roland, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Bechtle, Robert, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Brodsky, Eugene, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Brooks, Bruce, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Butterfield, Deborah, [Volumes I-II], circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
      - Clarke, John Clem, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Cone, Davis, [Volume 1]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
      - Falsetta, Vincent, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Han, H. N., circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Hanson, Duane [Volume I]-Volume IV, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 55, Folder 2-5)
      - Hoffman, Martin, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Horn, Gerald, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Hsia, Yan, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Jacobson, Gary, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Kessler, Alan, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - King, Tony, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Kolibal, Stanislav, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Koutroulis, Aris, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Kreznar, R. J., circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Li-Lan, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Nakagawa, Naoto, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Quasius, Sharron, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Radetsky, Jack, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Roje, Arsen, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Shaffer, Mary, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Artists' Slides, 1960s-2000s; 7.2
    - Artists' Slides, Current - Group A (Box 58)
      - Baeder, John, 1970s-2000s (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
      - Castanis, Muriel, 1970s-1990s (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
      - Chard, Daniel, 1980s-2000s (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Constantine, Greg, 1980s-2000s (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
      - Del Grosso, James, 1980s-2000s (Box 58, Folder 11-12)
      - Dudley, Randy, 1980s-2000s (Box 58, Folder 13-15)
      - Dufresne, Leonard, 1970s-2000s (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
      - Fox, Stephen, 1980s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1970s-2000s (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
      - Giese, David, 1980s-2000s (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Ginder, Robert Glen, 1980s-2000s (Box 59, Folder 8-10)
      - Goings, Ralph, 1969-2000s (Box 59, Folder 11-15)
      - Goings, Ralph, 1969-2000s (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
      - Gozu, Maso, 1980s-1990s (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Harrison, Allen, 1980s-1990s (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Hughes, Manuel, 1980s-2000s (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Jason, Jonathan, 1980s-1990s (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Jo, Sook Jin, 1980s-2000s (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Kacere, John, 1969-2000s (Box 60, Folder 8-10)
      - Lee, Daniel, 1990s (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Lynds, Clyde, 1980s-2000s (Box 60, Folder 12-13)
      - McClean, Richard, 1960s-2000s (Box 60, Folder 14-17)
      - Mendenhall, Jack, 1970s-2000s (Box 60, Folder 18-19)
      - Montgomery, Steven, 1990s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Müller-Franken, Johannes, 1995-2000s (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Nichols, William, 1980s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 3-6)
      - Pfannerstill, Tom, 1990s-2002 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Richards, Joseph, 1981-1987 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Richbourg, Lance, 1970s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
      - Rohm, Robert, 1969-2000s (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
      - Saari, Peter, 1970s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
      - Salt, John, 1969-2000s (Box 61, Folder 15-17)
      - Sato, Masaaki, 1980s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Szeto, Keung, 1970s-2000s (Box 61, Folder 19-20)
      - Van Patten, James, 1980s-2000s (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Van Vranken, Robert, 1980s-2000s (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Zago, Tino, 1979-2000s (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
    - Artists Slides, Current - Group B (Box 62)
      - Adams, Allan, 1970s-1980s (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Bacher, Tom, 1980s-1990s (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Baladi, Roland, 1970s-1980s (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Bechtle, Robert, 1960s-2000s (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
      - Bond, Douglas, 1970s-2000s (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Brooks, Bruce, 1982-1984 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Bultot, Roger, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Butterfield, Deborah, 1970s-1980s (Box 62, Folder 15-16)
      - Cho, Y. J., 1980s-2000s (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Clarke, John Clem, 1960s-1980s (Box 62, Folder 18-19)
      - Cone, Davis, 1970s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
      - De Andrea, John, 1970s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
      - Del Rosario, Mariano, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Douke, Daniel, 1970s-2000s (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
      - Falsetta, Vincent, 1984-1995 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - German, Vladimir, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Hall, D. J., 1970s-2000s (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Han, H. N., 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Hanson, Duane, 1960s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
      - Herman, Alan, 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Horn, Gerald, 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - Hrycun, George, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Hsia, Yan, 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Jacobson, Gary, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Kagan, Larry, 1990s-2000s (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Kelly, Jay, 1980s-1990s (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Kessler, Alan, 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - King, Tony, 1970s-1980s (Box 63, Folder 23)
      - Kolibal, Stansilav, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Koutroulis, Aris, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Kreznar, R. J., 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Krugman, Irene, 1970s (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Lakeman, Oscar, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 4-5)
      - Lazarevic, Milo, 1983-1992 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Levine, Marilyn, 1970s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 7-8)
      - Mackiewicz, John, 1980s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Morgan, Kenneth, 1970s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 10-11)
      - Okamoto, Kikuro, 1980s (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Okshteyn, Shimon, 1990s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Penner, Rod, 1990s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 14-15)
      - Quasius, Sharron, 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Radetsky, Jack, 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Richards, Joseph, 1970s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Rodriguez, Victor, 1990s (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Rudich, Richard, 1980s (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Shaffer, Mary, 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Sorce, Anthony, 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Souza, Al, 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Szeto, Keung, 1990s-2000s (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Vaadia, Boaz, 1980s-1990s (Box 64, Folder 25-26)
      - Wesselman, Tom, 1980s-1990s (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Wilkerson, Jerry, 1970s-1980s (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Installation Views, 1969-2014; 7.3
    - Photo Books (Box 65)
      - Installation Views (1969 October-1970 May), 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (1970 May-July) (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views II (Dismantled, 1970 June-1971 April), 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views III (1971 March-October) (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Installation Views IV (1971 October-1972 January), 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Installation Views V (1972 January-October) (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Installation Views VI (1972 October-1973 February), 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views VII (1973 March-November) (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views VIII (1973 November-1974 February), 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views IX (1974 March-June) (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views X (1974 September-December) (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views XI (Dismantled, 1975 January-June) (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Installation Views XII (1975 September-1976 January), 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views XIII (1976 January-June) (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views XIV (1976 September-1977 January), 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views XV (1977 February-June) (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views XVI (1977 September-1978 January), 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views XVII (1978 February-April) (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views XVIII (1978 April-November) (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views XIX (1978 November-1979 March), 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views XX (1978 April-1979 July), 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views XXI (1979 September-1980 January), 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views XXII (1980 February-July) (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views XXIII (1980 September-1981 January), 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views XXIV (1981 February-July) (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (1981 September-1982 February), 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views XXVI (1982 March-1983 January), 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (1983 February-November) (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views (1983 December-1984 September), 1983-1984 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views (1984 September-1985 April), 1984-1985 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (1985 May-1986 June), 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views (1986 September-1987 June), 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (1987 September-1988 July), 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Installation Views (1988 September-1989 July), 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views (1989 September-1990 June), 1989-1990 (Box 71, Frame 2)
      - Installation Views (1990 September-1991 June), 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (1991 September-1992 June), 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views (1992 September-1993 July), 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (1993 September-1994 July), 1993-1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Installation Views (1994 September-1995 July), 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views (1995 September-1996 July), 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views (1996 September-1997 July), 1996-1997 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (1997 September-1998 July), 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views (1998 September-1999 July), 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (1999 September-2000 July), 1999-2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Installation Views (2000 September-2001 July), 2000-2001 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Installation Views (2001 September-2002 July), 2001-2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Installation Views (2002 September-2003 July), 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views (2003 September-2004 July), 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views (2004 September-2005 July), 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (2005 September-2006 July), 2005-2006 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views (2006 September-2007July), 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (2007 September-2008 July), 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - "No Chromophobia" (2008 May 31-July 12; 2008 September 2-6) (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Installation Views (2008 September-2009 July), 2008-2009 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Installation Views (2009 September-2010 July), 2009-2010 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Installation Views (2010 September-2011 July), 2010-2011 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Installation Views (2011 September-2012 July), 2011-2012 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Installation Views (2012 September-2013 July), 2012-2013 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Installation Views (2013 September-2014 April), 2013-2014 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Installation Views - Negatives and Slides (Box 74)
      - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #19256-28688, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 74, Folder 7-9)
      - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #19256-28688, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
      - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #28886-37887, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 75, Folder 5-11)
      - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #38363-46625, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 75, Folder 12-13)
      - Installation Views by Dan Lenore - Negatives and Slides, circa 1969-circa 2014 (Box 75, Folder 14-15)
      - Installation Views - Negatives and Slides, 1997-1998; 12 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 75, Folder 16-17)
      - Views of Exhibitions at OK Harris Artists In Other Venues, 2003-2007 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - OK Harris Exhibition (2006 June 3-July 14; 2006 September 5-9) - Negatives (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1970s-2002; 7.4
    - Photo Book - Gallery Artists, Group Exhibitions, and Art Fairs, 1970s-2002 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Photo Book - OK Harris Offices, Staff and Exhibition Space, 1970s-2000s; undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - OK Harris Gallery, Interior Views and Kitchen Space - Slides, 2002; 1982-1983 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork - Negatives, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
- Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers, 1961-2012; Series 8; 4 Linear feet Boxes 75-79
  The Ivan C. Karp papers consist mainly of journals that record travel and daily life. There are a large number of obituaries from print and internet sources along with other biographical information, published versions of brief interviews with Karp conducted for various purposes, writings, a few materials relating to business and academic activities, and some photographs.
  The majority of this series consits of photocopies of Ivan C. Karp's journals from the period 1950-2012 (bulk 1991-2012). The earliest are travel journals written during trips to Italy, Spain, France, and more unusual destinations such as Bulgaria, Tunisia, Egypt, Poland, and Guatemala. The observant and thoughtul young Ivan Karp included salient details of travel and everyday life. Some entries are accompanied by drawings, and his interest in wordplay is evident. Later daily journals, written when Karp was an established art dealer, are more organized and less personal. Photographs, clippings, maps, and wine labels are occasionally included to illustrate statements or add interest. He wrote about scheduled activities, food and wine, sports, music, politics, and often commented on the weather. While daily journals record travel experiences at home and abroad, little mention is made of family or friends.
  Writings by Karp include articles, introductions and essays for exhibition catalogs, and a chapter in a book about the business of art. Among the writings by others is I Married an Art Dealer by Marilynn Karp. Also found are an academic paper, "Reflections on American Super Realism and Photo Realism" by Michael Jucker, and a dissertation by Suzanne Pines, "Five Photo-Realists: Process and Perceptions" (Columbia University, 1979). Among the small number of photographs are several digitial copies of earlier images of Karp including him in uniform during World War II and several at his gallery.
  - Resumes and Bibliographies, 1976-2012 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Obituaries and Appreciations, 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Obituaries, Internet, 2012 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Interviews with Ivan C. Karp, undated; 1984-2009 (Box 76, Folder 8-9)
  - Writings by Ivan C. Karp, 1963-2012; undated (Box 76, Folder 10-13)
  - Writings By Others Relating to Ivan C. Karp, 1991-2002; undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Book by Marilynn Karp, 2014 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Academic Paper by Michael Jucker, 1988
  - Dissertation by Suzanne Pines, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Anonymous Arts Recovery Society File, undated; 1961-2002 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Artist Guest House Records File, undated; 1983-2010 (Box 77, Folder 2-3)
  - Photographs, circa 1975-2012 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Journals (Box 77)
    - Travel Journals (Box 77)
      - Holland, England, Ireland; "Parables" Opinions, Observations on Various Subjects (circa 1950-circa 1954), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Sicily, (1933 [not found]); Spain ([1953],1958), France (1958), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Calabria, Sicily, Sardinia, London (1962 July-August), 2007 (Box 77, Folder 7)